candidatepoint.com 2019-06-24

# CandidatePoint | Privacy

Last modified: March 26, 2018

CandidatePoint respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website located at www.CandidatePoint.com and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing your information. 

This policy applies to information we collect on this Website. It does not apply to information collected by: a) us offline or through any other means, including on any other website owned or operated by CandidatePoint; or b) any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from our Website. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for any updates. 

You may contact CandidatePoint at 427 East 17th Street, Suite F - #734, Costa Mesa, CA 92627 or via our contact form located here. 

## Information We Collect

We may collect several types of information from and about the users of our Website, including: 

a) Any information by which you may be personally identified, such as username, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, resume and contents thereof, job search history, and any other data included in a submitted profile, resume, or search; 

b) Any information directly from you which you provide to us, such as survey information, ratings, reviews, questions, and answers; and 

c) Information may be recorded automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, clicks, page views, and search queries. We may store this information in our equipment, or the equipment of third party technology providers. 

## How We Use Your Information

We, or companies we partner with, may contact you based on your interests such as job postings and career development opportunities. Our Website may require you to provide us with contact information (such as your name and email address) as you register for our services. For the purpose of identifying users and delivering relevant content and advertisements, our partner LiveRamp may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser or a unique ID for your mobile device. To opt-out of LiveRamp cookies, please go [here](http://liveramp.com/opt_out/). 

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction. We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide to us as described to our subsidiaries and affiliates, to service providers and other third parties we use to support our business, but who are all bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose to them. We reserve the right to disclose any information as required by law, to comply with any court order, law or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request. 

We may use other companies as necessary to perform services required for our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Every effort will be made to safeguard your privacy when it may be accessed by other companies, including but not limited to technology providers; however, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. 

## Email Communication

You may receive email communication from CandidatePoint or our partners regarding job alerts, account notifications, promotions, and other communications by email. By registering on our Website and submitting your information, you are consenting to receiving email communications. 

If you do not want to receive particular types of email messages from CandidatePoint, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email message to notify us of our preferences, or click here. 

## Children's Privacy

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under the age of 13 may provide any information to the Website. We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 17 ask and receive permission from their parent or guardian prior to using our Website or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

## Protect Yourself

We strongly encourage you to exercise caution when providing information about yourself to others online, including when you register and use our Website. 

We want to take the time to remind you to never provide your social security number, credit card information, bank account details, or unnecessary personal information to a potential employer. Never participate in a financial transaction of any sort with a potential employer. Always be cautious of opportunities that sound too good to be true or require you to act as a financial intermediary, particularly for an overseas person. 

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. CandidatePoint may use cookies to keep track of your session and advertising delivery. CandidatePoint or our partners may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save a password associated with a user profile. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use third-party cookies to record information (excluding your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites and directly in emails/communications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on others websites. Our partners may also link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, hashed version of your email address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. You can learn more [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can opt-out of this type of advertising [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/). 

## Links to Third Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other external websites. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those external websites. You acknowledge that we are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that CandidatePoint is not responsible for the content of such external websites. Your use of external websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the external websites. 

## Assignment

If there is a change of control in our business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including personal information, could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the site, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of CandidatePoint or the assets of CandidatePoint. 

## Conditions of Use

Should you decide to use our site or services, you acknowledge and agree that your use and any possible dispute over your privacy is subject to the terms and conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

## Contact Information

If have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
